[{"answer": "I'm in good shape.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "What is your view of this debate right now and what should be done?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, you know, they're not evil people.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Does it depress you that even following a massacre as we saw at Sandy Hook School, there are still so many Americans who want no change at all?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm talking about the NRA.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "The NRA you're talking about?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Because they marshal money for the opponents, and they have been successful in defeating candidates.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Why are politicians so cowed by the NRA?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, I believe that we're not doing enough to deal with the national debt.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Where does it need to get to quite quickly, do you think, to maybe get back on its feet properly?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Well, firstly, I want to say this: I don't think he's anti-Semitic.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Why were you so animated?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "In terms of the Israel/Palestine situation, I mean, do you think that any kind of lasting peace settlement can be achieved without --", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "So why would we want to jettison -- which is really the way I feel he's acting -- the only democratic state in that area that we can rely on, Israel, in exchange for having the sheikhs and the kings and the presidents in Egypt and Lebanon and Syria and Iraq toasting with orange juice Hagel's appointment?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "You want me to tell me the truth or do you want me to stroke you?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Of course, the Israelis --", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Can only they change it or do the Israelis have to also give a little bit?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Worse.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "When you see it now, is it as bad as it's ever been, do you think?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I am for Hillary.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Could we be facing our first female president?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well, I am for term limits, but I'm for three terms.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Bill Clinton would still be president, wouldn't he?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Well, I am for Christine Quinn, but it's a wide open race.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Who would be the next mayor of New York?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Very, very tough.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Pretty tough act to follow, isn't he, Michael Bloomberg?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Not too well.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "How am I doing?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "It's on a subway stop, too.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What do you say?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "OCH: It is the only operating cemetery in Manhattan.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What was the thinking behind that?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Well, I want to tell you, I -- I'm secular but I believe in God.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "When you look at your own grave, which is something that very, very people ever do, Mr. Mayor, what do you think when you look at it?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Is that what it says?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "I'll tell you.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What has been your biggest failure, do you think?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Yes, it was.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "That was in Harlem, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "This is a great Super Bowl.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "As a kind of rookie myself in the world of Super Bowls, why is this one going to be special, as the commissioner seems to suggest?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What are the big issues surrounding the Super Bowl that you think America will be talking about?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "The beer is very important.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "What else do I need to really be an American watching the Super Bowl on Sunday?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I -- well, guacamole reminds me of mushy peas, which we have in chips in England, so maybe I'm a guacamole kind of guy.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "What's going to be in the Piers Super Bowl celebration here?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I'm fine, Piers.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Pat, how are you?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Very good.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "'BRIEN: Well, the Super Bowl in America is -- should be a national holiday.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Where do you put this one?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Well, the one where they all have to wear helmets and padding, right?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I think you're exactly right.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What is really going on between these two?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Well, I used to like the 49ers a lot until I got here.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "But where are you seeing this one go?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "No, I mean, the -- yes, good question.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Or is it really time that the sport got to grips with this and did something about it?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "There's only so much you can do.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "If you were running it, would you bring in any new regulations to try to limit the impacts?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "It -- I didn't feel anything, which is actually a lot worse because then I had this like blank look on my face.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Tell me what you were thinking as it began to fall apart?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "No, it's a tiered dress, which I didn't understand until I was like, why can I see my thighs.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Is it actually ripping?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "I had a million dreams.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "When you were a little youngster, what was the dream for you?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I grew up in Louisville, Kentucky.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "But tell me about your upbringing, your family, and what they make of all this?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Now they're very relieved.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "How do they feel now?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "I think there's a soulfulness that's immediately there.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "What does she have, Jennifer, that takes it to that kind of level?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "About half a second.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "How many seconds did it take to say yes to that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What me?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I'm Jennifer's little monster.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "My God, this doesn't get any better?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Maybe, Jennifer, you could explain to me why Harvey's a rascal?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "You and nincompoop.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Oh, God, what are these pictures?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Well, Meryl Streep, obviously.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "In terms of acting, who are your great inspirations?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Can you get past Bradley's good looks?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "He gave me tips once of -- on trying to stand my ground more and try to be like, no I want this.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "How does it work?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "That's a horrible question to ask a director.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Who do you think, David, is, pound for pound, the best actor in the world right now?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "That's like asking your favorite baby.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "That's like choosing your favorite baby?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "You're talking about actors and actresses?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Yes, I agree.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "Every girl loves a British accent.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "I also love England.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Isn't that true?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "Yes, I have.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "You've spent a lot of time there, haven't you?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130202pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "You eat fish and chips?", "qSentId": 728}]